{
    "subject": "resource/New_Order",
    "predicate": "ontology/genre",
    "object": "resource/Synthpop",
    "human_readable": "The genre of New Order is Synthpop.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.5431157350540161,
            "question": "Can you name a genre associated with New Order?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.539276659488678,
            "question": "Which genre defines the sound of New Order's music?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5382096767425537,
            "question": "What musical genre is New Order known for?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.46458524465560913,
            "question": "New Order's music falls under which popular genre?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.42343807220458984,
            "question": "If you enjoy electronic music with catchy melodies, what genre might you be interested in besides Synthpop?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4024369418621063,
            "question": "What type of music does New Order play?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.398393839597702,
            "question": "What kind of music is characterized by synthesized sounds and often a danceable beat, like New Order's?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.36770686507225037,
            "question": "How would you describe the musical style of New Order?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.3507069945335388,
            "question": "What is the primary style of music produced by New Order?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.29272595047950745,
            "question": "To what musical category does New Order belong?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=The genre of New Order is Synthpop.",
            "html": "dbpedia_6039_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What is the primary style of music produced by New Order?",
            "html": "dbpedia_6039_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=How would you describe the musical style of New Order?",
            "html": "dbpedia_6039_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What kind of music is characterized by synthesized sounds and often a danceable beat, like New Order's?",
            "html": "dbpedia_6039_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6039_108.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6039_112.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6039_139.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6039_146.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6039_148.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6039_16.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6039_26.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6039_32.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6039_67.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6039_88.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```  \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe information in the documents supports this triple. The text mentions that New Order is a pioneering band of the synthpop genre, and their influence on the genre cannot be overstated. It also discusses how their unique blend of electronic beats, melodic basslines, and introspective lyrics helped shape the synthpop genre."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe documents provide information that supports the statement \"The genre of New Order is Synthpop.\" Specifically, it mentions that New Order was at the forefront of the synthpop movement and became pioneers of the synthpop genre with their unique blend of electronic beats, melodic basslines, and introspective lyrics."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "More Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}